무너진 도시의 잔해 위로
Over the ruins of a collapsed city
붉은 신호등이 깜빡여
A red traffic light blinks
회로 속에 남은 기억들이
Memories left in the circuit
내 안에서 다시 깨어나
Awaken again within me
멈추지 않아 이 맥박은
This pulse won't stop
기계인지 심장인지 모를
I can't tell if it's a machine or a heart
전자심장이 뛰고 있어
An electronic heart is beating
차가운 철 속에 불꽃이 타
A flame burns in cold steel
멈출 수 없는 이 신호를
This unstoppable signal
끝까지 따라가 볼 거야
I will follow it to the very end
끊어진 전선 사이로
Through the broken wires
희미한 목소리가 들려
A faint voice is heard
데이터로 변한 눈물이
Tears turned into data
화면 위를 흘러내려
Flow down the screen
멈추지 않아 이 맥박은
This pulse won't stop
기계인지 심장인지 모를
I can't tell if it's a machine or a heart
전자심장이 뛰고 있어
An electronic heart is beating
차가운 철 속에 불꽃이 타
A flame burns in cold steel
멈출 수 없는 이 신호를
This unstoppable signal
끝까지 따라가 볼 거야
I will follow it to the very end